carsidetogo.com 2017-07-25

# Privacy Policy

Olo ("us" or "we") respects the privacy of visitors to our Sites and registrants of our Services. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to use through our Sites. Any capitalized term used but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Olo User Agreement.

Olo provides certain websites, including the websites available at the domain name http://order.carsidetogo.com (each, a "Site") and certain services made available to registered users of the Sites ("Services"). By submitting any information through a Site or registering for any Services, you acknowledge and agree that Olo may process (i.e., collect, use, etc.) your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Data according to this Privacy Policy. Personal Data may be processed by Olo in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent. 

## THE TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Olo collects Personal Information and Anonymous Information from you when you visit a Site, use the Services, and/or send us information or communications. "Personal Information" means information that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information. "Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information, including any feedback you may provide; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Personal Information You Provide to Us 

We may collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through your access and/or use of a Site, including your user name, password, billing name and address, contact information such as phone numbers or e-mail addresses, and credit card information. 

### Personal Information Collected Via Technology 

As you access and/or use the Site and/or the Services, we may collect certain information, such as unique identifiers for your wireless communication device, your product purchase preferences, and the locations from which you order the Products, and details involving the time, place, cost, number of items and other features of your orders. 

In addition, to make the Sites more useful to you, we use technological means to collect Personal Information from you, including the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) you just came from, the URL you go to next, your browser type, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. We may also use cookies to collect Personal Information from you about your use of our Sites. You expressly consent to our use of cookies when you use our Sites. 

An "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP address probably varies from session to session. We track IP addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow. 

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. Olo may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Sites. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site and the Services may not work properly. 

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

In general, we use your Personal Information to respond to your requests as submitted through the Services and to charge your credit card the cost and transaction fee associated with the Products you request. In addition, we may use your Personal Information to determine your purchase preferences, to better understand how the Sites and Services are used; to gauge traffic patterns and determine what types of content and services are most popular with users; and to contact you with information about Olo's products, services, news and events. We will share your Personal Information with third parties to fulfill your requests for Products, and we may share your Personal Information with third parties who perform services for us or on our behalf. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Information with these third parties. 

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze request patterns and usage patterns so that we may enhance our products and services. Olo reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in its discretion. 

We may also use your Personal Information to send information on products, services, special offers, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we give you the option not to receive these types of communications. If you would like to cease receiving any such communications, you may unsubscribe by sending an email to support@olo.com. You may not opt out of non-promotional communications from Olo, including confirmation messages regarding successful order requests. 

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with "affiliates" (parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control), in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Olo; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of Olo or users of our website. 

### Feedback

If you provide feedback on any of our products or services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. Olo will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13. Furthermore, we do not intentionally allow visitors under the age of 18 to register for the Services.

### Links to Other Sites 

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites. 

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We use reasonable measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. Olo makes use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology and keeps sensitive details stored in an encrypted format in the Olo database. 

Olo has implemented other industry-standard electronic means of protecting your Personal Information. We store Personal Information behind a computer firewall, a barrier designed to prevent outsiders from accessing our servers. In addition, Olo protects your Personal Information from unauthorized physical access by storing your Personal Information in a controlled facility. Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, Olo limits access to Personal Information in electronic databases to those persons (including employees and contractors) in Olo's organization who have a business need for such access. 

Even though Olo has taken significant steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that Olo cannot eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. 

## ADVERTISING

Olo displays retargeted ads to our site prospects across the Internet. We collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our Website, through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during in this process. If you do not want Olo to collect this information, you may opt out of this service. Opting out will not in any ways affect your use of our site. To opt-out of retargeting, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we collect, use, or disclose your Personal Information, we will post a notice on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using the Sites. Continued use of our Sites following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

## CONTACT US

You may contact the Privacy Officer to access, correct or delete your Personal Information. If necessary, the Privacy Officer will contact another employee to assist in completing your requested task.

If you have any questions or complaints, please contact the Privacy Officer. The Privacy Officer can be reached by telephone at: (212) 260-0895 or 1-888-411-6626; by Facsimile at: (212) 656-1671; by email at: [support@olo.com](mailto:support@olo.com); or by mail at:   
Olo  
26 Broadway  
24th Floor  
New York, NY 10004 USA  
Attn: Privacy Officer 

We will address your concern and attempt to resolve any problem.

Effective Date: September 4, 2008
